[music]
Hello hello everyone today we are going to talk about risk
management which is for intraday and
swing trading in intraday
that first of all we have to set our timing from
15 minutes and unload the chart
after finalizing the chart on our first stock which
means ST here we should have a stop loss of
0.6 on any stock price
our stop loss will be 6 and the
target for that will be 0.5% so
if we talk about the second stock then
our stop loss on the setting stop will be
0.5% along with that our target will
be 0.5% if we trade on the third stock then its
stop loss will be 0.5 and its target will be 1%
we have to wait only for 0.5% and 1% in Android
if it goes more than that then it
is good if it does not happen then we have to unite
like this if we talk about swing trading and long
term so see first of all we have to
Fundamental stops have to be taken
for swing trading
like Reliance, HDFC Bank, Infosys,
Wipro, Bajaj Finance, in all this we have to
first select the best bike price,
even after flattening the best price,
our top loss should be three
percent, if you have a long term vision, then even if it
comes from three percent to five percent, then
we should average in it and not be
out of stop loss, if
I talk about target target, then in swing trading we can easily get
six to seven percent, even if we do
n't get it, if we get three percent
interest, then it is a very good thing
that we get only 4% return, if we get Rs
2357 in trading, then it is
very good, for the subscriber, it can also be done, along with this I will
talk about
ICC,
what has to be done in this, see, first we take the one
day chart, after taking the one day chart,
we analyze it,
what is its best bike price, that is,
I put a horizontal stop and we
saw that its
price is going up, that is  283 something
now see here there is a great opportunity to talk
if we add patient to it and
wait then in a few days,
in 15-20 days of the month its first
target will be 362 if it crosses this then
it can go up to 40 also if its
stop loss has to be kept then it will have to be
kept up to 270 only if you keep a long term vision
like 3 years, 5 years it
can give them very good returns every year thank you so
much